telugutalks.com 2016-11-06

# Telugu Talks.Com

### Privacy Policy

Telugutalks.com is fully committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.Telugutalks.com does not collect or save any personal information. Telugutalks.com does not use forms and all emails are completely deleted once they have been handled.We do not place cookies on the computers of visitors to our site.We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason.We do not maintain any databases storing any personal information about our visitors.Since we do not maintain any personal information about our visitors, we will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about this site.

### Aggregate Information

Telugutalks.com uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is used to enable us to improve and expand the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site.Telugutalks.com does not provide any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site.

### Advertising

Telugutalks.com use a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of Age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. We are at our free will to change and Revamp our policies without prior notices, to suite the requirements and updates From time to time.

### Your agreeing & your Consent:

By using our site, you agree to our websites privacy policy and By accessing and browsing our Site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions, please do not use Telugutalks.com Site. We strictly not pirate/infringement any digital content.

If you have any concerns email us at [Info@telugutalks.com](http://www.telugutalks.com/contactus)
